STANISLAV ZHDANOVICH

Web Developer



CONTACTS

Phone Number:

+375298792506

Email:

stasbarinoff@gmail.com

Address:

Minsk, Belarus

ABOUT ME

Started programming in 2016. 5 year of web development experience, 4 year mainly as a React developer. Confident knowledge of HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React. Studied independently and also graduated from Rsschool and MyFreedom Front-End/React development courses. I enjoy working in a team environment and learning new technologies. In addition, i've a lot of experience in the design and production of audio and video.

LANGUAGES

Russian

English

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front End Developer

MRSoft / Minsk / Dec 2019 - Dec 2020

3 Different Projects

- · Developing plugins
- · Developing new features
- · Backend support and development
- · Project support
- Unit Testing
- · Code review
- Code refactoring
- · Project architecture development
- · Interviewing new employees
- · Search and discussion of valid solutions at meetings
- · Implementation of UI components together with designers

Front End Developer

Arateg / Minsk / Dec 2020 - Dec 2021

3 Different Projects

• Full frontend development cycle (from nothing to the final customer's product)

Front End Developer

Exadel / Tbilisi / Dec 2021 - Present

1 Project

- Team Lead of Front End Team
- Development and Bug Fixing
- Unit Testing
- · Code Review
- Architecture
- Interviewing New Employees

EDUCATION

React Developer
Minsk & Myfreedom IT-School
2018

Front End Developer
Minsk & The Rolling Scopes School
2019

Bachelor Minsk & BDAM 2020

SKILLS

HTML
React
Redux
Material-UI
React-query
Jenkins
GitHub
GitLab
Figma
i18n

JavaScript

CSS
Typescript
NextJS
Apollo Client
Ant Design
Storybook
BitBucket
Webpack
Swagger
Jest